[
  {
    "question": "ناروتو أوزوماكي",
    "response": "ن ا ر و ت و أ و ز و م ا ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسكي أوتشيها",
    "response": "س ا س ك ي أ و ت ش ي ه ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساكورا هارونو",
    "response": "س ا ك و ر ا ه ا ر و ن و"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيتاتشي أوتشيها",
    "response": "إ ي ت ا ت ش ي أ و ت ش ي ه ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيناتا هيوغا",
    "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا ه ي و غ ا"
  },
  {
    "question": " مونكي دي لوفي",
    "response": "م و ن ك ي د ي ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "زورو رورونوا",
    "response": "ز و ر و ر و ر و ن و ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "نامي سوان",
    "response": "ن ا م ي س و ا ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "سانجي فينسموك",
    "response": "س ا ن ج ي ف ي ن س م و ك"
  },
  {
    "question": "تشوبر ماشو",
    "response": "ت ش و ب ر م ا ش و"
  },
  {
    "question": "جوتوجو تشو",
    "response": "ج و ت و ج و ت ش و"
  },
  {
    "question": "كاكاشي هاتاكي",
    "response": "ك ا ك ا ش ي ه ا ت ا ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "جيرايا ناميكازي",
    "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا ن ا م ي ك ا ز ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "توبي مادارا",
    "response": "ت و ب ي م ا د ا ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "أوتاكاتشي إتشي",
    "response": "أ و ت ا ك ا ت ش ي إ ت ش ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "ناغاتو زانتسو",
    "response": "ن ا غ ا ت و ز ا ن ت س و"
  },
  {
    "question": "أوتشيمارو سينجو",
    "response": "أ و ت ش ي م ا ر و س ي ن ج و"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيريشا هاشيدا",
    "response": "إ ي ر ي ش ا ه ا ش ي د ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "ميناتو ناميكازي",
    "response": "م ي ن ا ت و ن ا م ي ك ا ز ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "تسونادي سينجو",
    "response": "ت س و ن ا د ي س ي ن ج و"
  },
  {
    "question": "رين جوبيتو",
    "response": "ر ي ن ج و ب ي ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساي تينجي",
    "response": "س ا ي ت ي ن ج ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "شيكامارو نارا",
    "response": "ش ي ك ا م ا ر و ن ا ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيتشيغو كوروساكي",
    "response": "إ ي ت ش ي غ و ك و ر و س ا ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "روك لي ناروتو",
    "response": "ر و ك ل ي  ن ا ر و ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "غارا ساباكو",
    "response": "غ ا ر ا س ا ب ا ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساكي ناروتو",
    "response": "س ا ك ي ن ا ر و ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "شيناتشي كوسامي",
    "response": "ش ي ن ا ت ش ي ك و س ا م ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "هاشيراما سينجو",
    "response": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا س ي ن ج و"
  },
  {
    "question": "كونوها سينجو",
    "response": "ك و ن و ه ا س ي ن ج و"
  },
  {
    "question": "جينما كوتشيكي",
    "response": "ج ي ن م ا ك و ت ش ي ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "هيروشيما تشوجي",
    "response": "ه ي ر و ش ي م ا ت ش و ج ي"
  },
  {
    "question": " اوبيتو اوتشيها ",
    "response": " ا و ب ي ت و ا و ت ش ي ه ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "رينكو أكاي",
    "response": "ر ي ن ك و أ ك ا ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "كيريتو كيريجايا",
    "response": "ك ي ر ي ت و ك ي ر ي ج ا ي ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "إسكانور كين",
    "response": "إ س ك ا ن و ر ك ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "كانيكي كين",
    "response": "ك ا ن ي ك ي ك ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "ريزو كمويتو",
    "response": "ر ي ز و ك م و ي ت و"
  },
  {
    "question": "ساسوكي كين",
    "response": "س ا س و ك ي ك ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "شوتو تودوروكي",
    "response": "ش و ت و ت و د و ر و ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "أليس كوزومي",
    "response": "أ ل ي س ك و ز و م ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "توكويا غينكا",
    "response": "ت و ك و ي ا غ ي ن ك ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "سورين كاموي",
    "response": "س و ر ي ن ك ا م و ي"
  },
  {
    "question": "رينا كوريسونو",
    "response": "ر ي ن ا ك و ر ي س و ن و"
  },
  {
    "question": "توكا كيريشيما",
    "response": "ت و ك ا ك ي ر ي ش ي م ا"
  },
  {
    "question": "نيكو روبين",
    "response": "ن ي ك و ر و ب ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question": "سانجو بلاك",
    "response": "س ا ن ج و ب ل ا ك"
  },
  {
    "question": "روبين نيكو",
    "response": "ر و ب ي ن ن ي ك و"
  },
  {
    "question": "نامي نامي",
    "response": "ن ا م ي ن ا م ي"
  }
]
